thedailyheel.com 2017-06-06

# thedailyheel.com Privacy Policy

##  THEDAILYHEEL.COM PRIVACY POLICY 

_Last updated: October 14, 2015_

Thank you for visiting our website. Your privacy is important to us, and we have adopted this Privacy Policy to memorialize our data collection, use and disclosure practices for our website located at the [http://thedailyheel.com](http://thedailyheel.com/) domain, along with its related tools and services (the “Website”). The Website is owned and operated by Audience Drive, LP (“AudienceDrive,” “we,” “us” or “our”). This Privacy Policy applies to anyone using or browsing our Website and to information provided to us via the Website by you or other visitors or users of our Website (“you” or “your” or “users”). 

**CONSENT**

By using or accessing any part of the Website, including uploading submitting any content such as comments, text, images, videos, contact information, and any other content or information (“Your Content”), you consent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any provision of this Privacy Policy, you may not use or access the Website. 

Information collected through the Website may be transferred, used and stored in the United States and in foreign jurisdictions in which we, our users, or our service providers for the Website are located now or at any time in the future. If you access the Website, you consent to the capture, storage, transfer, use and processing of your Personal Information (as defined below) in and between all of those jurisdictions. The data protection and other laws in some countries and jurisdictions (such as the federal laws and some state laws in the United States) are not as comprehensive or stringent as the privacy laws in other countries and jurisdictions (such as the laws of the European Union). You agree that all transactions relating to our Website shall be deemed to have occurred in the United States, where we currently have all of our personnel and operations. 

**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION; THIRD PARTY SITES**

We may collect Personal Information in connection with our Website, such as through our contact pages and commenting features. You may always choose not to provide Personal Information, but this may prevent you from receiving certain services. When we use the term “Personal Information,” we mean information that can be used to identify an individual and may include your full or partial first and last name, postal business or home address, electronic email address, user ID, password, telephone number, fax number, and Your Content, to the extent that it identifies you or a third party. 

Our services may integrate with social media platforms, such as Facebook, Twitter, and Google, and if you choose to connect a social media account to our Website, then we will collect authentication information that permits us to connect to your social media account. We may also collect information form your social media account (such as your name, email address, demographic information from your profile, posting or other content, and your profile picture). 

We may also collect “Non-Personal Information” about you. “Non-Personal Information” means information that is not Personal Information, including, without limitation, aggregated and anonymized information. Examples of the Non-Personal Information we may collect include, but are not limited to: your IP address; information about your operating system and browser (such as maker and version); information, content, or advertisements you view, hover over, or click on; and the city and state (but not precise geographic location) in which you are located. We will not use Non-Personal Information to try to identify you, and if we associate any Non-Personal Information with information that personally identifies you, then we will treat it as Personal Information. 

Information may be collected by us or by one of our service providers but in either case, this Privacy Policy will govern the collection, use, and sharing of the information. 

Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices, or content of websites owned by others that may link to or that may be linked from the Website (Third Party Sites”). Accordingly, we encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of use of Third Party Sites so that you understand how those websites collect, use, and share your information. 

**USE OF INFORMATION**

We may use Personal and Non-Personal Information to improve online operations; provide customer service; provide newsletters and/or other communications or services which you have signed up for or otherwise agreed to receive; display advertising and other content that is customized to your apparent interests or preferences; send account- or transaction-related communications such as welcome letters and transaction confirmations; perform research and analysis aimed at improving our products, service and technologies; and manage our systems. We may also use this information for internal purposes to help us diagnose problems, monitor traffic patterns, and otherwise continually improve our Website and related services. 

Please note that when you initially sign up or submit information on our Website, you may receive email messages or newsletters from us. You will be given the opportunity, in any commercial email that we send to you, to opt out of receiving such messages in the future by using the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of each such communication. It may take up to 10 business days for us to fully process an unsubscribe request, and we may send you other types of transactional and relationship email communications, such as requests for additional information, confirmations, service updates or announcements, and administrative notices without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

**DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

We may disclose Personal Information and Non-Personal Information about you to companies, agents, contractors, service providers or others engaged to perform functions on our behalf (such as providing data storage, hosting the Website, processing payments, conducting audits and performing web analytics, and fulfilling orders or requests that you initiate), and to market our other products and services to you (for example, to send you messages concerning new Website features or special offers). 

We may also disclose your Personal Information to third parties, in our sole discretion, to: (a) enforce or apply the Terms, including investigations of potential violations thereof; (b) comply with legal or regulatory requirements or a governmental request; (c) protect the rights, property or safety of AudienceDrive, our users, or other third parties; (d) comply with a request by any authority, such as a police department or regulatory authority; or (e) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical problems that may arise. We may also disclose Non-Personal Information to our clients, developers, business partners, merchants, advertisers, investors, potential buyers and other third parties for any reason in our sole discretion. 

We reserve the right to transfer information (including your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information) to a third party in the event of a reorganization, spin-out, sale, merger, or transfer of some or all of the assets of our company, or in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, liquidation or receivership of our business. However, we will provide you with advance written notice in the event any such transfer would subject your Personal Information to materially different privacy practices. 

**CHOICE; ACCESSING AND UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

When you use our Website, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your Personal Information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backups), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case, where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. For information about your choices regarding targeted advertising from third party advertising networks, please see the section below on “Cookies and Automatic Data Collection; Advertising Networks.” 

Please email us at [privacy@audiencedrive.com](mailto:privacy@audiencedrive.com) or contact us at the address stated below with any questions if you need assistance accessing or changing your Personal Information or if you would like to have your Personal Information deleted from our servers. Please be aware that if you delete your Personal Information, you may not be able to continue to use the Website. If you ask us to delete your Personal Information, we may in our sole discretion retain certain information, including your Personal Information, to satisfy our legal, audit and/or dispute resolution requirements. We may also retain your Non-Personal Information indefinitely. 

**COOKIES AND AUTOMATIC DATA COLLECTION; ADVERTISING NETWORKS**

Non-Personal Information (including aggregate, technical or demographic information) can also be collected through the standard operation of our internet servers and logs as well as other automatic data collection tools such as “cookies,” “web beacons” and other similar web technologies. A “cookie” is a small amount of data that is recorded either temporarily or persistently on your hard drive and that a website can use in order to recognize visitors who revisit the website so as to facilitate their ongoing access to and use of the website. Information we may collect through cookies and other similar technologies includes your browser type, language preference, operating system, referring website (if applicable), your IP address, the name and type of your computer or mobile device, the operating system of your device, your general geographic location, the date and time of each user visit or request, and the Website endpoints that you accessed or visited during your use of the Website. In addition to other uses as described in this Privacy Policy, we may gather the information we collect from each user and perform statistical analysis of the aggregated information, including analysis about the behavior of visitors to our Website on an aggregated, anonymous basis. 

Any Non-Personal information we collect from you through the use of our cookies, web beacons and other web technologies may also be used by us and shared with our affiliated companies to target advertising to you on the Website. We may also allow unaffiliated third-party companies such as advertising networks to serve ads and/or collect anonymous, Non-Personal Information when you visit our Website. These unaffiliated third-party companies may collect and use Non-Personal Information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. This collection and use of Non-Personal Information would be governed by those unaffiliated third-party companies’ own privacy policies. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacons to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt out of this type of advertising for participating companies, you can visit **[http://www.networkadvertising.org.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)** Please note that if you delete your cookies or use a different browser, a different computer, or other device, you will need to opt out of this type of advertising again. 

We support the development and implementation of a standard “do not track” browser feature that provides customers with control over the collection and use of information about their web-browsing activities. Once a standardized “do not track” feature is released, we intend to adhere to the browser settings accordingly. 

You may prevent our use of cookies to collect Non-Personal information about you by adjusting the option that is available in most web browsers to deny or accept cookies. Recognize, however, that cookies may be necessary in order to provide certain features such as the customized delivery of certain information to you. 

**CHILDREN**

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children less than 18 years of age. Nor do we authorize or permit children less than 18 years of age to use the Website. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 18, upon receipt of notice from the child or the child’s parent or legal guardian, we will delete that child’s Personal Information and/or disable such information from being viewed or accessed by any other user or other third party. 

**INFORMATION SECURITY**

We utilize a number of reasonable information security measures to safeguard your Personal Information. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet and no method of data storage can be guaranteed to be secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we do not guarantee its security. 

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

A California resident who has provided Personal Information to a business with whom she or he has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes (“California Customer”) is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed her or his Personal Information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of Personal Information, upon receipt of a request by a California Customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom Personal Information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of Personal Information that were disclosed. 

Currently, we do not intend to share your Personal Information with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. 

Please note that whenever you choose to share your Personal Information with a third party or to allow your Personal Information to be shared with a third party to communicate with you, your information will be subject to the third party’s privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use your Personal Information and other information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information. 

California Customers may request further information about our compliance with California’s privacy law by emailing [privacy@audiencedrive.com](mailto:privacy@audiencedrive.com) or contacting us as stated below. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer per year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this email address. 

**YOUR CONTENT**

Please note that when you choose to upload or submit Your Content, such as by posting comments, messages, and other content on the Website, Your Content will be viewable by third parties and other Website users and, in the case that Your Content consists of images, photographs, comments, and communications in public online forums, is publically viewable. Accordingly, you should exercise discretion with regard to what Personal Information you post on the Website through any means, and should not post personal, highly confidential, or sensitive information (such as Your Content that is identifiable or embarrassing to you or others). We are not responsible for how third parties who view Your Content may use any Personal Information contained therein, such as to send you unsolicited messages. 

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may modify or update this Privacy Policy periodically by posting an updated policy on the Website, which modifications will become effective immediately upon posting. You can always check the “last updated” date at the top of this document to see when the Privacy Policy was last changed. We may also post a notice concerning changes to the Privacy Policy on our website if there are material changes. We encourage you to check this Privacy Policy regularly. 

Your continued use of the Website following the effective date of an updated Privacy Policy constitutes your consent to the contents of such policy. However, we will not apply any material changes retroactively to any information we collected from you before such changes took effect, without your affirmative consent to do so. **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO FUTURE CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST STOP USING THE WEBSITE AFTER THE EFFECTIVE DATE OF SUCH CHANGES.** Please note that upon you ceasing use of the Website, any Privacy Policy in effect immediately prior to your departure shall continue to be binding on you and applicable to the data (including any Personal Information) collected from you prior to such departure. 

**CONTACT US**

To ask questions about our Privacy Policy, obtain more information, or to lodge a complaint, please contact us at: 

Audience Drive, LP  
Attention: Office of the General Counsel  
116 Pine Street  
3rd Floor, Suite 320  
Harrisburg, PA 17101  
Email: [privacy@audiencedrive.com](mailto:privacy@audiencedrive.com)
